[A Dream Within A Dream]
[Episode 16]
Are you restless
because of the marriage between
the Song and Chu families?
It's not difficult.
Doesn't Song Yude have a second daughter?
If you can't marry Song Yimeng,
then marry Song Yiting.
There's always a second option.
No.
Why not?
Song Yiting is meticulous
and intelligent.
If I marry her,
won't I be asking for trouble?
Being meticulous
and intelligent
are the character traits of a good wife.
Do you have to marry a crazy woman
like Song Yimeng?
Song Yimeng is pretending to be crazy.
Those are her tricks to hide herself.
That's strange.
Instead of an intelligent wife,
you want a cunning woman
who pretends
to be crazy.
It doesn't matter.
What matters is to stop the marriage
between the Song and Chu families.
Then marry both daughters.
Marry a virtuous wife
and have a pretty concubine.
Ridiculous!
With all due respect,
if you want to fight for the throne,
you mustn't waste your time on love.
With your tactics,
it won't be difficult to
ruin this marriage.
Why bother being upset
and affecting the important plan?
Your Highness,
your attendant is too hot-tempered.
He crossed
a high-ranking official's daughter.
Please
take a look.
Why didn't you stop her?
You haven't learned your lesson
from last time?
No,
Chief.
It’s not my fault.
Miss Song
came in with the notice for the
method of weapon forging.
Who dares to stop her?
What notice?
Don't tell me you took an important thing
like the method of weapon forging
and posted it all over the streets.
I didn't put that up.
Don't yell at me.
Who else could it be?
[A few days ago]
Go secretly find
knowledgeable people
and see if anyone
can read these words.
Okay.
Yunlong,
find the clues in secret.
If you can't find it,
don't bother coming back.
Got it?
Shanhu,
find clues.
What is this gibberish?
Where can I find any clues?
What if I can't find any?
Yunlong already told me
that if you can't find any clues,
he'll chop your head off.
Yes.
Chief has given the order.
If any of you can't find any clues,
he'll chop off your head.
I have a lot of work to do,
so I had Yunlong and Shanhu do it.
But I didn't expect
they'd be so stupid.
Yes,
you're not stupid.
You're just lazy!
I didn't save you from
the celestial prison
for you to be a freeloader.
Wait.
Mechanical arm.
Hurry up.
You're so slow.
This...
Are you doing this on purpose?
-Let me.
-How many times has it been?
Let me do it.
You are so stupid.
Don’t move.
Mr. Li!
Let me.
You’re pressing my hair.
Be gentle.
S-Sorry.
Excuse me.
No.
He...
Song Yimeng!
Hey.
Miss Song!
Miss Song, just now...
Mr. Li.
Just now...
You don't have to explain to me.
You...
It's not a big deal.
Don't be nervous.
I understand everything.
What do you understand?
No,
I just...
Chief.
What do you want?
What are you doing?
The notice.
Clues.
Second Master said
I must report intimately.
I'm talking to Miss Song.
Let's talk about it later.
Chief!
The new guys from
the northwest are here.
They're all so muscular.
Most importantly, they have good skills.
Do you want to give it a try?
We'll talk later.
No,
he's talking about weapon forgers.
Weapon forgers?
I understand.
I understand it all.
I understand everything.
What do you understand?
You don't look like you understand.
He's talking about weapon forgers!
He...
Shangguan He, come here.
Hurry. You're just in time.
Now,
tell Miss Song
about everything that just happened
in the room.
I can't tell her about
your identity change, right?
Mr. Zhang from the west of the city
came to see you.
He said
the lives of his three sons
are in your hands now.
Please treat them...
Gently.
Okay.
I told you to explain what happened
in the room.
Did you explain it to her?
Wait,
what should I explain?
Mr. Li,
you really don't have to explain to me.
I understand.
Don't show
this thing
to others again.
Since you are...
You are...
You...
You all...
I...
You...
Take it as my wishful thinking.
In the future,
let's never meet again!
Song Yimeng!
No, I...
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
I...
No wonder
your men
said you're not interested in women.
No wonder
you're with that
Shangguan He all day long.
And that day,
you let me take a look at the wound.
It's late and we're alone.
We'd better keep a distance.
But that's Chief's private domain.
But don't worry.
There are definitely no women there.
The Chief doesn't like women!
So that's where you hide your lover.
What a pity.
My love
has ended
before it even started.
Song Yimeng.
You're here?
My bestie.
Sit down.
Have a seat.
It's dangerous to drink on a rooftop alone
in the middle of the night.
Let me tell you.
I thought you were good to me
because you liked me.
I didn’t expect this, Mr. Li.
I didn’t expect
you only see me as a bestie.
It's not what you think.
I...
Shush!
There are so many people here.
It won't be good if they hear your secret.
It's bad for you.
Understand?
Enough.
Listen to me, Song Yimeng.
Listen to me carefully.
I...
don't like men.
Do you hear me?
You...
don't like men?
Yes.
So you just
simply like Shangguan He?
Are you an idiot?
If my relationship with Shangguan He
is like that,
then is everyone in Waning River Crescent
blind and can't see it?
What's wrong?
You don't only like Shangguan He?
Who else?
Yunlong
and Shanhu?
Or is it that...
That...
Those Northwestern boys?
I mean...
Alright.
Don't say anything.
I’m afraid it’ll be harder
for me to accept it.
I know, Mr. Li.
You can’t force yourself
to like someone.
I know all of this.
I really know.
So,
me liking you
is just
my own business.
It has nothing to do with you.
No matter what kind of person you like,
or whatever,
in my heart,
you’ve always been the best.
You're the best.
I’ll always support you.
Really.
Cheers.
So no matter what I say,
you won't believe me?
Then I'll prove it to you.
♪ If frost etched traces of weariness ♪
♪ If surging clouds hid the stars ♪
♪ The gaze you once cast upon me ♪
♪ Does it still remember love and hate? ♪
♪ If the rising wind scatters the dust ♪
♪ If every dream must be awakened ♪
♪ How much of the past can we recognize? ♪
♪ In a single thought lies tenderness ♪
♪ Look at the vast heavens,
letting rain fall, indifferent to all ♪
Do you believe it now?
♪ Watch how time quietly
waits for stories to take root ♪
♪ Look at the way you're going,
destiny has it all planned out ♪
♪ We lead remarkable lives
in this mundane world ♪
I'm speechless.
Your qin skills are excellent.
You expressed the great passion
of Mr. Chu's sword dance piece.
The qin still can't express
the decisiveness of killing.
People say
our lady is extremely talented,
but I know
you have your own
ambitions in your heart.
In this case,
Mr. Chu is indeed
more suitable for you.
A martial artist
is despicable.
He's just a homeless dog.
Then,
do you like the Seventh Prince?
He's scheming
and calculative.
He's just a bug in the gutter.
In that case,
only the Eighteenth Prince is left.
Yinzhu.
Humans
can't fall in love with idiots.
They're another species.
Don't you understand?
Someone like me
should cultivate immortality.
It's a pity that my mother is forcing
me to get married
and fall into the mortal world.
My heart is full of sorrow.
I can't find solace.
Oh, moon,
since ancient times,
are you the only one
who understands my sorrow?
Sir, please wait!
♪ Phantom dragon
lurks in the black market ♪
♪ Radiant lanterns
illuminate the Nightwalkers ♪
Moon Immortal.
♪ In the dark of night,
pure dreams run deep and wide ♪
May I ask
where you came from
♪ Who dares to join the game?
This isn't child's play ♪
and where you're going?
Don't ask where I came from
♪ Footsteps that shake the sky,
fear refuses to fade ♪
or where I'll return to.
♪ Every punch lands
hard on this wild melody ♪
Rivaling the moon's glow,
sailing on the wind.
I didn't expect
that someone in this world
would ignore me.
Shannai,
within one day,
I want all of his information.
I was drunk last night.
You two carried me back to my room?
Did you see anyone else?
Someone else?
My Lady,
I don't know how you came back.
In the skies, may we be birds
flying side by side.
On the ground, may we be besties.
My Lady, you...
Don't worry about having no soulmates.
Best friends' feelings stretch
for millions of miles.
My Lady,
what's wrong?
You're rambling while looking like
you've lost your soul.
What should we do?
How could Li Shiliu
do this to you?
I think you should break up with him
and date General Chu.
My Lady, you have no idea
General Chu visits us every day
these days.
He's about to flatten our doorsteps.
How about
you meet him?
Meet him.
What a bad idea!
You're treating him like a backup.
What?
Forget about that.
You can't be depressed forever.
The best way is to heal a broken heart
is to cut off the old relationship
and start a new one.
If you don't like someone,
you have to reject them clearly.
Acting hesitant and ambiguous
is scumbag behavior.
Anyway, I've thought it through.
I will definitely break off
the engagement with Chu Guihong.
I won't get him involved.
Regardless of the fact that the marriage
is an imperial edict,
My Lady, think about it.
You've only liked Li Shiliu for a few days
and you’ve become like this.
Mr. Chu has liked you
for a dozen years.
Will he do something extreme?
Bravo!
What's going on?
Who are these people?
Mr. Chu,
what's this for?
The Waning River Crescent
posted notices without authorization.
The capital prefecture's office
is here to investigate.
Ridiculous.
What shop in capital doesn't post notices?
Mr. Chu paid a visit
just for
this small matter.
Tell Li Shiliu to come out.
Chief is not here.
I make the decisions
for Waning River Crescent.
Since Li Shiliu is not here,
we'll take you back to
the capital prefecture's office.
Guards!
Stop!
Mr. Chu,
didn’t we work together
on restorations a few days ago?
What's this supposed to mean?
The Qianyu Army received a report.
Last night at midnight,
you sneaked into the Song Residence.
Mr. Li,
can you explain
why you flipped over
the wall at midnight and even entered
the women's ward?
Mr. Chu,
didn’t you just say it's about us posting
notices without authorization?
Why is it about me breaking into
the Song Residence now?
I've been in and out of there many times,
but no one reported it to the officials.
I think
you brought so many people here today
to make a scene, right?
So what?
You told Yimeng to break off
the engagement with me.
Song Yimeng wants to
break off the engagement?
Stop pretending.
Yimeng is getting married with me.
Please stay away from her.
What if I refuse?
[Invitation]
The wedding invitation is here.
No matter how unwilling you are,
don't forget to come to our wedding.
I've been on the battlefield for years.
She has been waiting for me for years.
The wedding date
was decided by Mr. Song and His Majesty.
Li Shiliu,
no matter how capable you are,
you will never affect this marriage.
Mr. Chu,
since you are so confident,
let's make a bet.
I bet I can force you to
cancel
this engagement within 10 days.
[There will be a banquet at my residence
on March 18—Chu Guihong]
Didn't you just say yesterday
you didn't want to get
Song Yimeng involved?
Why did you make her
break off the engagement today?
Things are different now.
Elaborate.
How are things different?
Didn't you hear just now?
Song Yimeng
took the initiative to
break off the engagement.
She doesn’t want to get married.
I'm helping her.
I heard it clearly,
but I have to remind you.
Song Yimeng doesn’t want to
marry Chu Guihong,
but she doesn’t want to marry you either.
Let me put it this way.
She might've considered you
before yesterday,
but now,
because of our relationship,
I don't think so anymore.
Why are you so upset?
Listen.
From now on, stay three steps away
when talking to me.
Otherwise,
I'll stuff you back
into the celestial prison
like how I pulled you out before.
Understand?
Yes, yes.
You talk about sending me back every day.
You don't even spice things up.
No wonder you can't even
handle Song Yimeng.
[Song Residence]
You help me break off the engagement?
Do you think I'm a fool,
Your Highness?
If I break off the engagement
with Chu Guihong
and then marry you,
I'll be the one doing
all the offensive things.
You, on the other hand,
will get all the benefits
of a political marriage
and attacking your enemy.
Wake up, Your Highness.
Stop dreaming.
Song Yimeng,
when can you
be honest with me?
Am I not being honest?
I am.
Here.
Look at this.
The mechanical arm?
What did you do to him?
In your heart,
I'm just a cruel and merciless person.
All of this is normal for me.
Now,
I've only made him suffer a little.
But as long as I want to,
I can kill him anytime.
What makes you think
you can threaten me with him?
Stop pretending with me.
I have many spies in the capital.
I know clearly when you went to
Waning River Crescent,
and when you left.
As long as I want to,
I can also find out
what you said
to Li Shiliu.
As a prince,
you're really rich and idle.
Is a martial artist
worth all your efforts?
It's not him I care about.
It's you.
If you marry Chu Guihong,
the Song family
will definitely fall into Nan Rui's hands.
I'm doing this
to protect myself.
Now, Chu Guihong is holding
a sword over my head.
How can I just sit by and do nothing?
That's why you're threatening me
with Li Shiliu?
How despicable.
Whatever you say.
Anyway,
you have to listen to me.
Stop!
Do you really care about
Li Shiliu this much?
Could it be...
you like him?
Yes.
That's right.
I like him.
What does it have to do with you?
You like him so much
that you're not afraid
I'm manipulating you?
He won't like me anyway.
You can manipulate me however you want.
What if he likes you?
Would you marry him?
Hey,
are you really this bored?
Does this have anything to do with you?
It has nothing to do with me,
but...
I heard that Li Shiliu
and Shangguan He, the Second Master
of Waning River Crescent...
Shut up.
Don't worry about this.
Breaking off the engagement
is not that easy to do.
Give me some time
to think about it.
But before that,
if you dare to hurt Li Shiliu,
I'll make you die with me.
I'll keep my promise.
You hear me?
I thought you'd have to show up
personally as Li Shiliu.
Unexpectedly,
you only used one arm
and Song Yimeng agreed to do the rest.
Why are you still unhappy?
It's not that I'm unhappy.
I just think it's too smooth.
It's strange.
Doesn't Song Yimeng think
Li Shiliu and a loser like you...
Have that kind of relationship?
Then why would she be threatened by me
and break off the engagement?
If it weren't for a loser like me,
Song Yimeng wouldn't have
realized her feelings.
Look,
she knows it's impossible with Li Shiliu,
but she still protects him
without hesitation.
This is love.
Your Highness,
you finally understand love.
[Peace and Serenity]
Anyway,
this is the situation.
I won't marry
someone I don't like.
Father,
I think you should
break off the engagement.
Father,
what are you doing?
Stop!
This thing
was originally prepared
to negotiate with your stepmother, Zhou.
I didn't expect
my good daughter would force me
to this step today.
We can talk.
Come down first.
Don't fall.
What do you want to talk about?
I begged and pleaded
for this engagement's
imperial edict.
The emperor's fury
can cause a million deaths.
Do I have to watch as you jump into danger
and fall into the Seventh Prince's trap
to be used and tricked by him?
The love of parents
is a long-term plan.
Yimeng's mother,
I'm coming to join you!
Alright, alright.
Stop.
Please come down,
Father.
No need to speak further.
I don't need your help anymore.
You
don't need to threaten me with death,
okay?
Alright?
Come on. Get down.
Come down!
Unbelievable.
Your Highness.
Miss Song is here.
Bring her here.
Yes.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Didn't you swear yesterday that
you'd break off the engagement?
Are you here
to give me the good news?
Something happened
with my father.
Anyway, I failed.
Oh?
What?
It's because my father has sharp eyes
and knows you're a vicious villain.
He's sure we have something between us.
That's why he won't break it off.
Are you blaming me?
Of course.
You...
You're so cunning.
Give me an idea.
What should I do?
In the end,
you still need me.
[Song Residence]
Really?
It can't be wrong.
I paid
my cousin's
uncle's
cousin's
aunt's
nephew.
Get to the point.
The person who came to
the Song Residence that night
was indeed Li Shiliu.
The capital's top fighter
and Chief of the Waning River Crescent.
I've heard of him before,
but I didn't expect it
to be him.
My Lady,
it's been so many years.
This is the first time
you've ever met someone you liked.
Why don't we
go to Waning River Crescent now?
How about it?
Mother has been watching me closely.
I'm afraid I'll be brought back
before I arrive at a place
like Waning River Crescent.
You're right.
Yiting!
Madam.
Song Yimeng of the first wife's side
has started to prepare for marriage.
How come
there's nothing on your side?
Do you really want to
make Eighteenth Prince
wait until next year?
I'm talking to you.
I'll ask His Highness
to meet up at the Waning River Crescent.
Is that okay?
You finally got it.
How is it?
With my glamorous outfit today,
even if I say I'm the most handsome man
in Great Jing,
I'm afraid
it's not an exaggeration.
Jixiang,
you don't know,
but this is Yiting's
first time asking me out.
I'm afraid
she's finally broken through her fear
and can meet me with confidence.
It's not easy.
What if
she can’t help herself today
and proposes to me?
Should I agree to her immediately
or should I
delay it for a few days
and think about it
before I agree?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
This kind of trouble won't come to you.
Nonsense!
I...
Your Highness,
she's here.
Yiting!
Yiting,
you're here.
Slowly.
Here.
Let me help you.
Let's go.
Yiting, this way.
Yes.
You know the way.
A toad wants to eat swan meat.
The good cabbage has been taken by a pig.
What's this supposed to mean?
Your idea to break off the engagement
is horseback riding?
Your Highness,
you'd better give me a
reasonable explanation.
This is
the imperial stables.
The guards around here
are the Imperial Guards of His Majesty.
If I ride with you alone here,
then within an hour,
His Majesty will hear about it.
This trick again?
So old-fashioned.
How old a trick is doesn't matter,
as long as it works.
The problem is it doesn't work.
A scandal between us
is not enough
to make His Majesty cancel the engagement.
Didn't you fail last time?
You made such a commotion in the palace
and implicated Her Ladyship.
Now you're doing this again.
Aren't you afraid of
offending your father?
I've offended him many times.
Once more won't make a difference.
Come up.
We're riding one horse?
Help!
We're gonna crash!
Slow down!
I'm here.
Why are you so scared?
I'm not afraid of the horse.
I'm afraid of you!
Sky blue Ru porcelain.
Good taste.
Wang Muqing's painting
from the last dynasty.
It's indeed classy.
This table
is Siamese rosewood
with golden thread.
The craftsmanship is exquisite.
The owner of Waning River Crescent
is indeed a wonderful person.
Your Highness,
what's this for?
Miss Song,
pick to your heart's content.
I'll buy anything that you
have a fancy for
and send them to your residence.
Are you flaunting your wealth?
No.
I...
I'm not.
Can you
not be so mean when you see me?
I...
Jixiang, Jixiang.
Put these down.
Yiting,
I want to say
that I pay attention
to your words.
I never treat others like this.
You want to marry me.
Why?
Men and women should marry
when they become of age.
A gentleman pursues a beautiful woman.
What's the problem?
Eighteenth Prince, may I ask you
what marriage means?
It means...
Well...
Marriage
is when a man and a woman
are willing to accept each other
as their companion.
In sickness and in health,
for richer, for poorer,
they're willing to comfort,
protect,
love,
and respect each other,
never leaving
till death
do them part.
Wait, this...
Which famous
author wrote this line?
Song Yimeng.
My older sister,
Song Yimeng, told me this.
Miss Song,
are you playing with me?
You know very little about me.
You want to marry me
because you don't want to
lose to Seventh Prince.
If it weren't for the matter between
my sister and Seventh Prince
causing a stir in the city,
it wouldn't matter
whether you married
me or not,
right?
No.
Absolutely not.
I really like you.
And Father also thinks you are good.
You're the one getting married,
not His Majesty.
You keep talking about His Majesty.
Are you getting married
or is His Majesty getting another consort?
I... No.
I mean, I...
This...
I'm sorry.
Forgive me for being rude.
Yiting.
Yiting?
Hey,
did I not make myself clear?
It's only been an hour
and I've learned how to ride horses.
How is it, Your Highness?
Not bad, right?
It's because I'm a good teacher.
However,
the battlefield's war stallions
aren't as good as
the palace's tame horses.
On the battlefield,
there's not enough food for the horses.
Many of them are injured too.
In a battle, no matter if it's an arrow
or cannons,
they'll all affect
your control of the horse.
Don't make it sound so miserable.
Isn't it your choice?
Everyone knows that Seventh Prince
fights on the battlefield
to win military merits.
Am I right?
Yes.
Winning military merits and seeking fame.
You're right.
You sound sarcastic.
You won't believe me no matter what I say.
Everyone in Great Jing knows
His Majesty doesn't like me
because of the past.
If I don't go to the frontier
to kill the enemy,
is there any other way for me to survive?
Going to war is a dangerous thing.
Why is it
a means to save yourself?
When I was nine,
I was banished to the cold palace.
I'll starve you to death!
I was mistreated,
and went hungry.
I was even thrown into the fire
and had my food poisoned.
His Majesty knew about all of this,
but he never cared about it.
I won't kill you.
Chop off the hand
that you used
to break Rui's arm.
Or do you want people to insult me
as a tyrant who kills his subjects?
You are father and son.
How can you be such enemies?
There are no father and son
in the imperial court.
Everything I have now
was earned by fighting
through seas of corpses and blood.
With this kind of backstory,
it's no wonder his personality is twisted.
No, no.
How can I sympathize with him?
Song Yimeng,
don't be a Mary Sue.
Wake up.
We're in the capital now,
but we can't become out of shape.
Have our men
practice hard.
Yes, General.
General.
Look.
Here.
I can come down by myself.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Chu Guihong is here.
Don’t look.
A short pain is better than a long one.
Whether you can break off the engagement
or not depends on this.
What do you want to do?
What are they doing?
Nan Heng,
do you want to die?
Let go of me!
Do you hear me?
General.
Calm down.
He is a prince.
Nan Heng!
Let go of her!